developerdrive.com 2019-06-12

# Disclaimer and Privacy Policy - Developer Drive

**Privacy Policy Statement  
****Developer Drive (“DD”, “Website”) is committed to the security of your information and pledges to follow the terms set out in this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”).**

**Website Information Usage  
****We use web stat services to track the location, browser, operating system and screen resolution of our visitors, but not private information about each individual (such as your name of email address). E-mail addresses are only ever provided by the user voluntarily through the commenting process or via e-mail communications. Note: E-mail addresses that are entered in the required “e-mail” field in the comments area, are not publicly displayed.  We aggregate user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, and information volunteered by readers, such as survey information and/or Website registrations. The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Website in a technical fashion only and not for marketing purposes.**

**Public Information  
**Our Website enables you to post information to be accessed by others through our comments. When you do so, other visitors may collect your data and attempt to contact you off the site. Developer Drive cannot be held liable for any offsite communications that result from your posting of personal information on our site. If you do not wish to be contacted offsite by other Developer Drive visitors, do not give your e-mail address or website address in the content when leaving a comment. Please note: Although you are required to provide your e-mail address in the specified field  when entering a comment, your e-mail address will only be available to the Developer Drive website administrators and will not be publicly visible.

**Advertisers  
**Third-party advertisers featured on Developer Drive may collect tracking information in a different manner than is set out in this Privacy Policy. The only information that they will be able to track is basic Website usage information; e-mail addresses are not passed on to advertisers for any reason even if they are provided to Developer Drive voluntarily.

**Cookies  
**We use cookies to store visitor preferences, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, customize Website content based on visitor browser type or other information that the visitor sends.

**Use of Information Provided By User  
**If you have chosen to subscribe to our newsletter, you will receive email correspondence from us whenever we send out our newsletter (which is usually once a week). You may choose to unsubscribe from this email at any stage, via the unsubscribe link provided in each newsletter. Your personal information is not used by subsidiary organizations or businesses related to Developer Drive, unless clearly disclosed for specific situations.

**Information Ownership  
**All e-mails, comments or other forms of communication received by Developer Drive are the property of  Developer Drive and may be used for editorial or technical improvements to the Website at our discretion without any form of compensation being owed to the sender of said communications.

**Information Security  
****We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities and the facilities of our service providers to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our Website.** Information provided by Website visitors is held in confidence and used for editorial and technical improvements to the Website.

**Affiliate Programs, sponsored posts, etc  
**From time to time we may choose to use affiliate links and/or sponsored posts as an effort to generate extra income to our website. The appearance of such links or sponsored content in this blog is determined by its informational or inspirational value and not by its commercial value to us. We will only promote products and services that we like and feel are beneficial to our audience.

**Third party advertising  
**We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when users visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our site, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you.

**Privacy Contact  
****If you feel that this Website is not following this Privacy Policy, you maycontact us at with your concerns.**
